Absolutely interesting, and I think like there's people probably do
cool
things where they like
program keyboards to
automatically, like, you know, create forks or like auto,
you know, do machine learning to on their PCs so
they can like automatically detect things in this space like
you can do cool things with computation and electronics and
out in sensors. Whatever your game,
maybe we actually have a lot of people do cosplay
and like they want to have costumes that look like
their characters.
You can't cosplay as text venture.
I mean you probably could.
It'll be weird 'cause you just have like a lamp
and like a grew and it wasn't really look like
I don't know and like a piece of paper with
a map on it, right?
Like it's not. I mean,
I guess you
could. You could possibly,
but pretty obscure it. Be really sure.
I mean it, your little cook Dragon con 'cause he
would be like that's so obscure.
That's like the third character in like
yeah yeah. I mean like the people who would get
it would would get it right and they would be
so stoked.
That was just Oh yeah anyway.
So people like
to do do cosplay like a lot Cos play is
like they have to do a lot of electronics now.
Yeah, ever leads. The rings are glowing and like making
noises.
But they're not learning electronics and then doing cosplay.
They're doing cosplay now like I really want to make
this glowing sword that when I poke something with it,
it makes the noise that the sword makes in the
game.
You know it's Speaking of
like things that are glowing and gangs that are making
noise like all that kind of stuff.
So you've got this big warehouse in New York City
where everybody works in your company and I'm trying to
picture it in my head.
Like all of these parts,
all of these light bulbs,
all of these things like coming to life in this
warehouse.
I've
never seen a photo of it actually.
Can you describe what it looks like to us?
Yeah, so well, it
looks like it looks like every photo you've ever seen
in the attract manufacturing.
Now there's there's. There's the the main like engine.
Is this picking place line and the pick and place
line is something that basically takes circuit boards which are
these custom CAD design things look a lot like what
my background is on soon with you guys.
Can't see 'cause you're hearing my voice but it's got
traces on it when people think like circuit board style,
that's that's what it is.
Except it's designed to actually connect traces and components together
in the right order.
And I design those and send those out and they
get manufactured at a factory that does that and and
there is a chemical process.
We can't do it if you need to basically have
a set up to do it,
and he's doing a 24 hour so you can recycle
the chemicals,
which again would do. And they made the circuit board
with these components of components come on like reals like
they're just spun around on spools,
basically of components, and then they pick and place you
load it in,
and then it has these little pickup.